pcoptimizerpro.com 2016-03-14

# Privacy Policy- PC Optimizer Pro

|   
---  
  
This Privacy Policy is documented to inform the users of PC Optimizer Pro website regarding the manner in which PC Optimizer Pro  
("Xportsoft Technologies" or "We") gather, use and disclose their profile and anonymous information, and under what circumstances PC Optimizer Pro will disclose such information. 

PC Optimizer Pro will take reasonable actions to safeguard your ("user") privacy in agreement with the guidelines laid down in this privacy policy and with applicable United States laws.

This website Privacy Policy has been provided by the legal resource of the Company and has been reviewed and authorized by their attorneys. This Policy explicates what happens to any information you provide to PC Optimizer, or that it gathers from you at the time you visit this website.

We do update this Policy from time to time so kindly do review this Policy regularly.  
  
**Our Non-Disclosure Statement**  
  
PC Optimizer Pro is committed to protecting your profile information and other personal data you may share with us during the course of receiving our products and/or services. We respect your privacy and, to the extent possible, ensure the protection and non-disclosure of your personal information to any third-party service provider. 

We will not sell, trade, or rent your information to any third party. We will not disclose or misuse your personal information for purposes excluding those laid down in this Policy, unless we receive your consent to do so or we are legally obliged to do so, such as by law, court order, or subpoena, or unless such use or disclosure becomes requisite for the fortification of our legal interests.

By using our website, you consent to PC Optimizer Pro's collection, use and disclosure of personal information compliant with the guidelines set forth in this Privacy Policy.  
  
_Privacy Management_  
  
In accordance with foregoing statement, we will not collect, use or disclose personally identifying information regarding you without your knowledge, therefore the choice whether or not to share your profile information with us is completely reserved by you. 

Furthermore, you may at any time unsubscribe from PC Optimizer Pro mailing list, as explained later in this Privacy Policy, by following the information given in our newsletters and emails that you receive periodically. You may also request amendments in, or deletion of, your information by contacting us at [support@pcoptimizerpro.com](mailto:support@pcoptimizerpro.com). Note that any deleted information may stay in our records, database, or data store in consequence of custom system back-ups; however, this Privacy Policy certifies that any such information will not be used by PC Optimizer Pro.  
  
_Information Security_  
  
For the purpose of maintaining the security and integrity of information, we store your personal and profile information on computer systems that are non-public, have redundant firewall, and are password protected to prevent any unwanted access to your information by anyone outside authorized PC Optimizer Pro employees. PC Optimizer Pro has adopted stringent data security measures, as explained later in this document, to prevent any unauthorized access to your personal information.

PC Optimizer Pro, herein, appreciates your contribution in protecting the integrity, privacy, and security of your own information. We encourage you to inform us immediately what time you suspect that the information you shared with us is being used in any way, or for any purpose, other than those mentioned in this Policy. We will investigate and revert to your inquiry at earliest.

To contact us, send email to [support@pcoptimizerpro.com](mailto:support@pcoptimizerpro.com).  
  
**Enforcement**  
  
If you have sufficient reasons to believe that PC Optimizer Pro has not complied with the guidelines set forth in this policy, or in case you have any complaints regarding the gathering, use or disclosure of your information by PC Optimizer Pro, you can send a written complaint notice to: 

Xportsoft Technologies

Near Gugga Maadi, Khojkipur

Kardhan Road

Ambala Cantt

Haryana 133001

India

We will look into your complaint and will respond to you at earliest.

If you are facing any problems with our services or if you have any questions in regards to how our processes work, you can contact us by sending an email to [support@pcoptimizerpro.com](mailto:support@pcoptimizerpro.com).  
  
**Why We Collect Personal Information?**  
  
PC Optimizer Pro only collects your information where and when necessary to provide you quality products and services. 

Maintaining an organized record of our customer base helps us in providing you emails and other periodic notifications that keep you informed regarding the status of your accounts and/or orders. Moreover, it helps us in providing you technical notices, updates and technical assistance. These notifications are necessary for accurate maintenance of your orders, along with the features of our services and products.  
  
**Information We Collect From You and Its Use**  
  
For the purpose of running and maintaining this site, or for providing you our services, we may collect and process the following information about you:

    * Information relating to your use of our website, which may include the details of your visits like pages viewed and resources accessed. Such information may constitute of location data, traffic data and other communication data.
    * Information provided by you voluntarily. For instance, when making a purchase or registering to the website.
    * Information that you provide, or we collect, when you communicate with us through any means.

_Transmission of General Data over the Internet_  
  
To the amount your web browser, upon accessing any website related to the PC Optimizer Pro network, automatically transmits certain specific data which may include, but is not limited to, the time and date of access, accessed files, URL of the referring website, browser version and type, quantity of transmitted data, operating system (OS) information and/or your IP address, these information will be stored by PC Optimizer Pro separately from other personal information that you may provide to PC Optimizer Pro. This type of information can be evaluated by us for statistical purposes and will, then, be promptly deleted.  
  
_Information Collected Through Deliberate Submissions by Users_  
  
In case one or more of our websites offer a form allowing you to provide us your personal data or information which may include, but is not limited to, your name, date of birth, gender, email address, country, language, currency and product ratings, etc., our purpose of collecting such information will only be limited to delivering periodic promotional offers, discounts, marketing material and/or email newsletters on topics of interest to you.

In such case, if you do not want to receive such services or if you do not want your personal information to be used for such purposes, you are free to opt out of, or do not request, such services and disclosure compliant with this Privacy Policy.  
  
_Usage and Inventory Data_  
  
PC Optimizer Pro will acquire and use your personal data only if it is deemed necessary for providing its services to you, which may include completing any and all transactions.

PC Optimizer Pro further collects and uses your personal data only to the required extent to permit the billing for or, use of, its Internet services. In particular, such data, herein referred as "usage data" may include data relating to your identity and information indicating the start and conclusion of, and scope of, the usage of our Internet offerings. For the purposes of market research, advertising, and modifying of our internet offerings in accordance with market requirements, PC Optimizer Pro may create user profiles under pseudonyms. 

However, as the user of PC Optimizer Pro, you can, at any time, refuse the use of your personal data for such purposes, as further documented in this Policy. PC Optimizer Pro may not merge a user profile created under pseudonym with the personal data of the individual to whom the relevant pseudonym concerns.  
  
**Cookies**  
  
In order to facilitate the complete use of all the features of Internet offerings, PC Optimizer Pro makes use of alleged "cookies," which permit data to be stored on your system when you access any of our websites.  
  
_Use of Cookies_  
  
Cookies provide information regarding the computer used by a visitor. We may employ cookies wherever appropriate for the purpose of collecting information in regards of your computer to assist us in improving our website. 

We may gather information about your general internet use by using the cookie.  Where the use of cookies is applicable, they are downloaded and stored on the hard drive of your computer. Such information, however, will not be identifying you in person. Cookies are stored as statistical data only and does not identify your personal any of your information whatsoever.

Our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control.  Such cookies (if used) would be downloaded once you click on advertisements on our website.

You can adjust the settings on your computer to decline any cookies if so you want.  For doing so, you can activate the "reject cookies" setting in the Internet browser on your computer.  Also, to the extent you disagree with the use of cookies by PC Optimizer Pro, you may decline to allow cookies to be saved on your computer.  
  
**General Use of Your Information**  
  
We use the information that we collect from you to provide our services to you. In addition to this, we may use the information for one or more of the following purposes:

  1. To provide you the information you request from us in relation to our products and/or services.
  2. To provide you the information of other products that may be of your interest. Such supplementary information will only be provided where you have authorized us to send you such information.
  3. To inform you regarding any modifications in our site, goods, product or services.
  4. If you have previously purchased goods or services from us we may provide to you details of similar goods or services, or other goods and services, that you may be interested in.

Where your approval has been granted in advance, PC Optimizer Pro may permit selected third parties to make use of your data to allow them to provide you with information regarding unrelated goods and services which we believe may be of interest to you.  Where such authority has been granted it can be withdrawn by you at any time.  
  
**Storing Your Personal Data**  
  
In operating our website, it may become necessary to transfer data that we collect from you to locations outside of the United States of America for collecting, storing and processing. By making your personal information available to us, you express your consent to such transfer, storing or processing. We do our topmost to make sure that all reasonable measures are adopted for ensuring that your information is stored securely.

Alas, the transfer of information across the internet is not entirely secure and, now and then, information exchanged via Internet may be intercepted. PC Optimizer Pro cannot guarantee the security of information you choose to pass our way electronically.

Sending such information is entirely at your own risk.  
  
**Information Disclosure to Third Parties**  
  
_Forwarding to Google Analytics_

PC Optimizer Pro makes use of Google Analytics, an internet evaluation service by Google, Inc. ("Google"). 

Google employs the data stored by website cookies (as stated above) for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, for preparing reports of website activities carried out by administrators and for providing a variety of other services related to the internet and website usage. 

The processing of such data is done by Google on its servers based in the United States. Google, under certain specific circumstances, may provide the anonymized, compiled data to third party developers. 

You can review Google's scope and purpose of such analyses at [www.google.com/analytics/tos.html](http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html), and can read the data privacy policies of Google at [www.google.com/privacy.html](http://www.google.com/privacy.html).  

By using PC Optimizer Pro website, you express your consent to the process of forwarding of such data to Google and also to the processing of the collected information by Google. You agree that the data can be processed by Google for the purposes and in the manner described above. 

If you do not agree with this, you may anytime refuse or disable cookies from being saved and stored on your computer. However, profile information you provided to us is, still, subject to disclosure pursuant to laws applicable.

_Third-Party Service Providers to PC Optimizer Pro_

If in case PC Optimizer Pro contracts, or bundles its software, with any third-party service provider with the intent of providing some or all part of the data, offerings or services requested by you, PC Optimizer Pro may forward your information to such third-party service providers, or such third party may also request information from you on behalf of PC Optimizer Pro. 

In the event of forwarding your personal information, such third parties, however, are bound by written agreements by PC Optimizer Pro to adopt and implement similar and appropriate security measures for safeguarding your information as done by PC Optimizer Pro and are, thereof, only permitted to process your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Disclosing Your Information

In general, PC Optimizer Pro will not disclose or misuse your personal information to any party other than in accordance with this Privacy Policy and in the circumstances detailed below:

  1. In the event that we sell any or all of our business to the buyer. (Details below.)
  2. To further fraud protection and reduce the risk of fraud.

Kindly note that information provided to this website by you may be subject to disclosure pursuant to government or other judicial subpoenas, orders and warrants.  
  
**Opting Out of Use and/or Disclosure of Your Profile Information**  
  
PC Optimizer Pro will only make use of your information for the purposes stated in this Privacy Policy or for purposes subsequently sanctioned by you.

In case you want your profile information, which may not necessarily include the data required for the completion of any transaction initiated by you), to be removed from the database of PC Optimizer Pro, please feel free to contact us at [support@pcoptimizerpro.com](mailto:support@pcoptimizerpro.com) and we will delete your profile information.

_Information Access and Update_

Compliant with the US Data Protection Act, you hold the right to access any information that we hold relating to you. Please note that PC Optimizer Pro reserves the right to charge a nominal fee to cover costs incurred by us in providing you with the information. 

In the event you wish to review, modify, or delete your profile information from PC Optimizer Pro database, you may contact us at [support@pcoptimizerpro.com](mailto:support@pcoptimizerpro.com). 

Users of PC Optimizer Pro may review or amend their profile information as often as necessary and any time required, including the withdrawal of your approval to use your information to the limit you had earlier authorized. This may include opting out of your subscription for receiving the PC Optimizer Pro newsletter.  
  
**Data Security Assurance**  
  
PC Optimizer Pro has adopted appropriate security measures to protect your information from misuse, loss, unauthorized access, alteration, destruction and/or disclosure. Our security processes implement authenticated internal database access, procedure audit, and constant monitoring of complete web security.  
PC Optimizer Pro has multiple security measures in position, such as those stated below, in order to safeguard you against any kind of misuse, alteration, or loss of your information stored in our database.   
Information that you share with PC Optimizer Pro is stored in facilities that are secure and restricted to authorized PC Optimizer Pro professionals only.   
PC Optimizer Pro employs accurate access-control processes that are needed for the retrieval of our users' personal information. The website of PC Optimizer Pro is frequently analyzed for security breaches so as to prevent any unauthorized access to your information.  
Orders placed on this website for our products are processed by secure payment gateways to make sure your credit card and other personal details are secure during the processing of your transactions. The payment gateways or processors, such as ClickBank and PayPal, have their own privacy policy and process the transactions in accordance with the terms and guidelines set forth in their privacy policy. To learn more about how our e-commerce partners administer your personal information and other details of e-commerce transactions, you can review their privacy statements by visiting the links <https://accounts.clickbank.com/privacy.html> and [https://cms.paypal.com/in/cgi-bin/marketingweb?cmd=_render-content&content_ID=ua/Privacy_full&locale.x=en_GB](https://cms.paypal.com/in/cgi-bin/marketingweb?cmd=_render-content&content_ID=ua/Privacy_full&locale.x=en_GB).   
Note that the collection and use of your personal information by payment processors, payment gateways, or any other third-party service provider is compliant with their own privacy statements and PC Optimizer Pro is not responsible for any loss, misuse or damage of your personal information occurring in consequence of your dealings with them.  
PC OPTIMIZER PRO DOES NOT STORE YOUR CREDIT CARD INFORMATION. PC Optimizer Pro does not handle any transaction through the web; therefore, there is no need for PC Optimizer Pro to have streaming encryption products.   
PC Optimizer Pro has partnered with ClickBank that works as a trusted intermediary for handling our customers' e-commerce transactions. Our commerce partner maintains e-commerce and all related transactions on a secure server which is SSL secured to encrypt the personal information of our customers to prevent any unauthorized access.  
If, at any time, you would like to purchase any of our products, but do not wish to use your credit card for any reasons, you may contact our sales representatives through email at [support@pcoptimizerpro.com](mailto:support@pcoptimizerpro.com).  
Although we have adopted sincere measures to store and protect your personal information in a secure operating environment and, at all times, try to make sure your personal information is not open to unauthorized access, ensuring complete security is not possible and is therefore not provided to you as a guarantee.  
  
**Regarding Children**  
  
PC Optimizer Pro does not intentionally collect any profile information regarding visitors who are under the age of 13.   
  
**Acceptance**  
  
By using this website or any other service or product provided through this website, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information as explained in this Privacy Policy.   
  
**Miscellaneous**   

External Links  
On occasion we include links to third parties on this website. Where we provide an external link it does not denote that we endorse or approve that site's policy towards visitor privacy. Users should review the privacy statement of such external websites ahead of sending them any personal data.

PC Optimizer Pro website, therefore, may contain links to other websites. In such event, PC Optimizer Pro is not accountable for the content or privacy measures of those sites. 

Users need to be aware of this when they navigate from our website to an external link and should, in such case, review the privacy policies of the website they are visiting. This Privacy Policy is solely applicable to the collection and use of your information by PC Optimizer Pro.

_Transfer of Business_

PC Optimizer Pro is continuously trying to bring about improvements in its websites, products, services and business. 

If all or part of PC Optimizer Pro (or "Xportsoft Technologies") is merged, sold or otherwise transferred to another party, the information and data collected by PC Optimizer Pro from you may be transferred to the buyer as part of that transaction. 

In such event, PC optimizer Pro will oblige that the information be used by the buying entity in a manner that is in agreement with this Privacy Policy in effect at the time you provided PC Optimizer Pro with the information.

_Modifications_  
PC Optimizer Pro may amend or modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any material amendments in the manner in which your information is gathered, processed or disclosed, PC Optimizer Pro will notify you of these amendments by e-mail or on the website and will provide you a link to the revised privacy policy.   
If you refuse to any of the amendments made by PC Optimizer Pro in this Privacy Policy subsequently, you can request us to delete your profile information from PC optimizer Pro database by contacting [support@pcoptimizerpro.com](mailto:support@pcoptimizerpro.com).

_Choice/Opt-out_

Users of PC Optimizer Pro who opt-in to receive our newsletters and other similar material may anytime unsubscribe themselves from our emailing lists by following the instructions provided at the end of any email they receive from PC Optimizer Pro  
  
**Contacting Us**  
  
Please do not hesitate to contact us regarding any matter relating to this Privacy Policy. You may contact us at [support@pcoptimizerpro.com](mailto:support@pcoptimizerpro.com).

Effective Date: [June 29, 2013].
